《法外情真》前情回顾
Previously on The Guardian
我有动脉堵塞了
I've got a little blockage...
五条动脉里堵了四条
four out of five arterial.
那你需要手术吗
So you need surgery?
露露怀孕了
Lulu's pregnant, and...
我只是希望你能陪伴
I just hope that you'd be around to be there...
在你孙儿的身边
for your grand kids.
我知道我已经做好了当爸爸的准备
I know that I'm ready to be a father.
我不想结婚就只是因为我怀孕了
I don't want to get married just because I'm pregnant.
我喜欢你
I like you.
当我有所心动的时候
When I feel something...
我希望能全心而动
I like to feel it.
能不能给我来一杯龙舌兰酒
Can I get a shot of Tequila?
911紧急呼叫
911 Emergency.
这儿有一个拿着枪的男人在对人开枪
There's a man with a gun,and he's shooting people.
你在哪儿  女士
Where are you, ma'am?
凯恩工业
Kane Industry.
是凯恩实业公司吗  对吗  女士
Kane Industries?Js that what you said, ma'am?
噢  天呐
Oh, God!
女士  你还在那儿吗
Ma'am? You're at Kane Industries?
他刚才又射中一个人
He just shot someone else.
你在哪一层  女士
What floor are you on, ma'am?
他正在房间里走  他在四处查看  我不能说话
He's walking down the room. He's looking around. J can't talk.
你还在在吗  有人吗
Are you there? Hello?
他刚才射中了他自己
He just shot himself.
结束了  他对自己开了枪
lt's over. He just shot himself.
- 早啊  格雷琴  - 早啊  法林先生
- Morning, Gretchen.- Good morning, Mr. Fallin.
- 你好啊  - 需要我帮您拿公文包吗
- How are you?- Can I help you with your briefcase?
- 我的公文包吗  - 对
- My briefcase?- Yeah.
不用了  我能自己拿  谢谢
No, I can handle it, thank you.
我要拿一杯黑咖啡  谢谢  不过
I'll take a black comee, though, please.
加奶油和两块糖  行吧
Make it cream and two sugars, all right?
好
Okay.
嘿  伯顿  你今天感觉怎么样
Hey, Burton, how are you feeling today?
嘿  杰克  你怎么样  我挺好的  谢了
Hey, Jake, how you doing? I'm good, thanks.
好  好  听着  我恐怕要带一些很糟糕的消息给你了
Good. Good. Listen, I'm afraid I've got some very bad news for you.
早
Morning.
噢  尼克  我能跟你聊一下吗
Oh, Nick, can I talk to you for a second?
泰德  你能在那儿坐一会儿吗  我马上就来
Ted, will you just take a seat over there? I'll be right with you.
那个男孩的父亲  今天上午在凯恩纸业射中了三个人
That kid Ted's father shot three people at Kane Paper this morning.
什么
What?
其中的两个人已经死了  而且他的父亲开枪打了他自己
Two of them are dead, and his father shot himself.
孩子不知道吗
He doesn't know?
不知道
No.
第三季  第十一集
法外真情
翻译   章鱼   哥
校对  油 球
特效  转轮 枪
我为什么在这儿
Why am I here?
泰德  这位女士是来自社区服务中心的
Ted, there's this woman from Social Services,
她有些话必须和你说  所以
and she has to talk to you, so--
可以  但是我为什么在这里
Okay, but why am I here?
嗨  泰德  我是苏珊娜
Hi, Ted. I'm Suzanne.
贝尔纳教练  你在这儿做什么
Coach Bernardo? What are you doing here?
就是  呃
Just, uh...
就是看看你怎么样了  孩子
Just seeing how you're doing, kid.
泰德  你的父亲卷入到了一起事件中
Ted, there's been an incident involving your father.
什么
What?
他受伤了  医生们正在尽力抢救他
He's been hurt, and the doctors are trying to help him.
那  发生了什么
Well, what happened?
他走了进去  还和一些人打了招呼
He walked in, and he said hello to a few people.
然后他走向了凯恩先生
And then he walked right up to Mr. Kane.
拔出了一把枪  然后他
And he pulled out a gun, and he just...
大家为了在那儿开晨会
Everyone was there for the morning meeting,
他朝着凯恩先生的头就开枪了
and he just shot Mr. Kane in the head.
然后他射中了珍妮  射中了文斯
And then he shot Jenny and then he shot Vince.
而且他对文斯开了三枪
And he shot Vince three times.
我很抱歉  安妮特
I'm so sorry, Annette.
呃  你想和比尔·詹姆森谈谈  是吗
Um, you wanted to talk to Bill Jameson, right,
是关于他这次对新闻界的声明吗
about his statement for the press?
对  出于法律的原因我们说话不得不谨慎一点
Right. We have to be a little careful what we say, legal reasons.
听着  安妮特  如果你有任何的其他问题
Listen, Annette, if you have any more problems,
只要你需要  随时打我电话
you need anything at all, just call me.
这是个直线电话  好吗
This is a direct number, okay?
好
Okay.
好了  坚持下去
All right. Hang in there.
- 好吗  - 好的
- All right? - All right.
- 谢谢你  - 保重保重
- Thank you. - Take care.
埃里克
Eric?
伯顿  嘿
Burton, hey.
还好吗  孩子
How you doing, son?
我还好
I'm good.
你父亲的事我感到很抱歉
I'm so sorry to hear about your dad.
- 你什么时候来的  - 我刚到这儿
- When did you get here? - I just got here.
你感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
噢  我  我不错
Oh, I'm--I'm fine.
我听说那个心脏手术了  那挺严重的
I heard about the heart surgery. That's some serious stuff.
嗯  我现在挺好的
Well, now I'm fine.
很难相信你已经可以起来走动了
Hard to believe you're already up and around.
是啊  我没事  谢谢你  你还能撑住吗
No. I'm fine, thank you. But how are you holding up?
我可以的
I'm good.
你不觉得你需要  呃  回家或者
You don't think maybe you should, uh... be back at home or--
我没事了  已经  我  呃
I'm good, really. l, uh...
我已经准备好和大家谈了  所以
I already talked to everybody, so...
噢
Oh.
好  听好  如果你妈妈需要什么
Well, listen, if your mom needs anything,
帮忙葬礼的事  或者其他一些事情  你要让我知道好吗
any help with the funeral or anything else, will you let me know?
伯顿
Burton...
我想完成和帕拉马尔的交易
I want to finish the Palamar deal.
这事儿比较急
There's a clock on this thing.
你现在不用担心交易的事
You don't have to worry about that right now.
我是说  我们可以延长这件事的时间
I mean, we can get that extended.
我想尽快召集董事会
I want to assemble the board as soon as possible
让他们批准我担任执行总裁
and have them approve me as CEO.
那  我觉得如果你休息一段时间会更好
Well, I was thinking maybe it'd be a good idea if you took a little time off.
你知道  我父亲为了这个单子已经忙了五年了
You know, my father's been working on this deal for five years.
- 我明白  - 所以你去安排和董事们开个会
- I understand. - So you'll get a meeting with the board.
好  我  我可能
Well, l--l probably--
好  谢谢
Good! Thank you.
好
Yeah.
那
Well--
打扰一下
Excuse me.
埃里克  这是约拿·西尔弗曼医生
Eric, this is Dr. Jonah Silverman.
他是一名心理学家  他想和你聊聊
He's a psychologist, and he'd like to talk to you.
你好
Hello.
感谢您的到来  西尔弗曼医生
Appreciate you coming down, Dr. Silverman,
但是我现在非常忙
but I'm very busy right now.
呃  埃里克
Uh, Eric--
安妮特  也许我们可以把和西尔弗曼医生见面
Annette, perhaps we can meet with Dr. Silverman
的时候更好的安排在我的日程表上
when it works better for my schedule.
当然  当然  等你准备好了再找我
Sure. Sure. Call me when you're ready.
好  呃  保重
Well, take, uh... take care.
他射中了三个人吗
He shot three people?
很显然  是的
Apparently, yes.
泰德  我们现在需要了解一些关于你
Ted, part of what we need to do right now is Iearn a little bit about you,
和你们父子之间关系的事
about your relationship with your father.
为什么
Why?
因为我们想帮助你
Because we want to help you.
你能告诉我你父亲在家生气的时候会怎么处理吗
Can you tell me how your father dealt with his anger at home?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我们不理解今天发生的一切
We don't understand everything that happened today,
但是事件发生时你父亲似乎非常生气
but it seems your father was very angry.
他会对你生气吗
Did he get angry with you?
会吧
I guess.
他曾经有打过你吗
Did he ever hit you?
没有
No.
对你大喊大叫呢
Yell at you?
有时会
Sometimes.
泰德  你曾经是否有觉得你会伤害别人
Ted, have you ever felt like you could hurt somebody?
- 噢  够了吧  不  停下  - 我们需要了解那样才能
- Oh, come on! No! Just stop! - We need to know so we can--
想想这个孩子正在经历什么
Think about what this kid is going through.
尼克  我们需要出去了
Nick, we need to go outside.
泰德  你和古普塔医生待在一起好吗
Ted, you stay with Dr. Gupta, okay?
尼克  尼克
Nick. Nick.
她需要问那些问题
She needs to ask those questions.
我知道它听起来有些不近人情  但是如果他受到过虐待
I know it seems insensitive, but if he's been abused in any way--
- 在里面的那个男孩需要他的母亲  - 她去世了
- That boy in there needs his mother. - She's dead.
- 他有其他亲属吗  - 不知道
- Does he have any relatives? - Don't know.
他和他父亲是两年前从明尼苏达州搬过来的
He and his father moved here from Minnesota two years ago.
听着  我需要回到房间  但是你可能应该等一等
Look, I need to get back in there, but maybe you should wait.
对  好  好
Yes, fine. Fine
- 我明天给你打电话  - 好的
- I'll call you tomorrow. - Good.
保重  泰德
Take care, Ted.
我现在能回家了吗
Can I go home now?
你需要在收容所待几晚
You'll need to stay in a shelter for a few nights.
我为什么不能和我的朋友待在一起
Why can't I stay with one of my friends?
今晚不行
Not tonight.
- 贝尔纳教练可以吗  - 今晚不行
- What about Coach Bernardo? - Not tonight.
让我们去你家拿一些你的东西
Let's just get you home, get a few of your things
然后带你去收容所安定下来好吗
and get you settled in at the shelter, okay?
- 你会来吗  - 我吗
- Will you come? - Me?
他们来了  他们来了
Here they come! Here they come!
也许我应该一个人进去
Maybe I should just go in alone.
我的房间在大厅后面
My room's down the hall.
好的
Okay.
呃  尼古拉斯
Hmm. Nicholas.
坐吧  孩子
Sit down, son.
你怎么样了
How you doing?
嗯  还好吧  我想
Well, okay, I guess.
我今天下午见过埃里克·凯恩了
I went over to see Eric Kane this afternoon.
那孩子还在震惊中
That kid's in shock.
他脑子里只想着谈和帕拉马尔交易的事
All he wanted to talk about was the Palamar deal.
他的父亲我一直不是很了解
His dad I never knew very well.
他曾经派他的亲信参加会议
He used to send over his henchmen to the meeting and...
那个禽兽
That animal.
他们说两周之前他们把开除了
They said they'd laid him off two weeks ago.
对
Yeah.
简直不可思议
lt's unbelievable.
一个男人用他所有的生活建立公司的点滴
Man works all his life building something up and...
他的公司就有一个人是这么做的
one of his employees does something like that.
你知道吗  爸爸  也许回来工作对你来说有些太快了
You know, Dad, maybe it's a little too soon for you to be back at work.
医生说了没事
The doc says it's okay.
医生是说兼职
Doctor said part-time.
我就是这么做的
That's what I'm doing.
好了  听着  我一直在想关于律师事务所的事
Well, listen, I've been thinking about the firm,
我觉得我们应该在这儿谈一谈转变了
and I think we should probably talk about a transition here.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
好吧  我一直跟我自己约定当我老了
Well, I always promised myself when I got older
我不应该再紧抓着不放
that I wouldn't hang on too long.
执行委员会这周五开了会议
Executive committee is meeting this Friday,
然后我提出了我想退位的意向
and I thought I'd propose that I step down.
你打算退休了吗
You're going to retire?
不  但是我觉得是时候任命你为执行合伙人了
No, but I do think it's time you be named managing partner.
我觉得我们现在应该行动了
I think we should act now.
好
Yeah.
你准备好了吗
You're ready.
对
Yeah.
那  有几件事你得弄清楚  但是  呃
Well, there're a few things you're gonna have to figure out, but, uh...
你准备好了  准备好了
You're ready. You're ready.
嘿
Hey.
嗨
你在盯着我看吗
Are you staring at me?
不
No.
我是不是有流口水什么的
I wasn't drooling or anything, was l?
没有
No.
噢  周五下午我要做另一个检查
Oh, Friday afternoon I have another check-up.
好的
Okay.
他们准备做另外一种超声波  呃
They're gonna do another ultrasound and, uh...
做些更多的测试和检查
take some more tests and stuff.
好
Right.
你想来吗
You want to come?
当然
Of course.
好
Good.
我还要在收容所待很久吗
Do I have to stay at the shelter much longer?
再待几周  或者更久
A few more weeks, maybe more.
那些孩子  他们已经知道我是谁了
The kids, they figured out who I am pretty fast.
他们一直在说我爸爸和我的事
They're saying things about my dad, and me.
你只能看他几分钟  好吗
You can only see him for a few minutes, okay?
好
Yeah.
我应该做些什么
What am I supposed to do?
你可以试着和他说说话
You could try talking to him.
他能听到我说话吗
Can he hear me?
也许吧
Maybe.
嘿  老爸
Hey, Dad.
我是泰德
lt's Ted.
我就快完成那个你喜欢的大帆船拼图了
I almost finished that puzzle of that schooner you liked.
但是我觉得我们丢了两片拼图
But I think we lost two of the pieces.
- 我想问问他  - 问他什么
- I wanted to ask him. - Ask him what?
是不是他做的
lf he did it.
他应该告诉我的
He would tell me.
我在报纸上看到了
I read in the paper.
上面说他朝一个人的脸上开了三枪
It said he shot a guy in the face three times.
是他做的吗
He did that?
对
Yeah.
埃里克  请进
Eric. Come on in.
- 你还好吗  孩子  - 挺好的
- How you doing, son? - I'm well.
- 你看起来不错  - 坐吧
- You look good. - Sit down.
呃  谢谢你给我妈妈寄的篮子
Uh, thanks for basket that you sent to my mother.
她说那很棒  还有那些花也是
She said that it was amazing. And the flowers, too.
好  好
Right. Right.
我们领情了
lt's appreciated.
谢谢
Thanks.
所以  你和董事会谈了吗
So, did you talk to the board?
埃里克  呃
Eric, uh...
我觉得我们都该明白  现在对你来说确实不合适
I think we all understand that this is not a real good time for you.
你说了你愿意联系董事任命我为执行总裁
You said that you would contact the board and get me appointed CEO.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
他们都把精力用在了  用在了葬礼上
They're all in town for the... for the funeral.
对  是
Yeah, right.
那是为什么
What is it?
埃里克
Eric...
你有没有找机会和那个创伤顾问谈一谈
Did you get a chance to talk to that trauma counselor?
那个人  那个来我办公室的家伙吗  西尔弗曼医生吗
The guy--The guy from the office? Dr. Silverman?
- 对  - 不  还没有
- Right. - No, not yet.
那你有计划休息一段时间吗
Are you planning to take a little time off?
- 完成交易后  也许会吧  - 也许会吗
- After the deal, maybe. - Maybe?
你知道我重视你才让你办这件事  伯顿  我重视你
You know, I appreciate your concern on this, Burton. I do.
但是我希望你能更好的完成身为我的律师该做的事  行吗
But I would prefer if you'd just act as my lawyer, all right?
我
l...
好了
Yeah.
嘿  尼克
Hey, Nick.
嘿  你怎么样了  埃里克
Hey, how you doing, Eric?
-  我很抱歉  - 谢谢
- I'm so sorry. - Thank you.
如果有什么我能帮上忙的
lf there's anything that I can do--
不  不  不  不  我们已经搞定了
No. No, no, no. We got it--We got it covered.
好吧
Okay.
我得走了  呃
I got to, uh...
你能和克雷格·休伯蒂的儿子聊聊吗
Can I talk to you a second about Craig Huberty's son?
他怎么了
What about him?
我作为这个孩子的代表在这家律所工作  呃
I work at this clinic that represents children and, uh...
我正在试着为他找个住的地方
I'm trying to find a place for him to live.
噢
Oh.
没有利益冲突  我只是想应该让你知道
lt's not a conflict. I just thought that you should know.
- 好的  - 抱歉了
- Okay. - I'm sorry.
有些事情我不得不做
lt's just something I have to do.
对  就是  呃
Right. It's just, uh...
一些你不得不做的事
something you have to do.
对
Yeah.
嘿  我不知道你有没有听说  呃
Hey, I don't know if you've heard yet. Um...
珍妮  我们的市场主管  她在三小时前死了
Jenny, our Chief of Marketing, she died three hours ago.
我猜她原本也是没希望活下来的
I guess she never really had a chance.
休伯蒂很直接的朝她的脑袋上开抢了  所以
Huberty shot her point-blank in the side of the head, so...
我要走了
I gotta go.
再一次表达我的哀悼
Again, my condolences.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 那孩子一团糟  - 是的
- That kid's a mess. - Yeah.
他想董事会成员选举他  成为新的执行总裁
He wants the board members to vote him in as the new CEO.
好吧  我能理解他
Well, I can understand that.
我不确定
I don't know.
他想回到工作中去
He wants to get back to work.
发生这样的事时他还能做些什么呢
What else is he gonna do when something like this happens?
问题是  我和董事会成员中的少数人谈了
Problem is, I spoke to a few of the board members.
他们对这个想法实在不感兴趣
They're not real excited about the idea.
埃里克知道吗
Does Eric know that?
我不确定
I doubt it.
他父亲一直都把他蒙在鼓里
His father kept him pretty much in the dark most of the time.
如果我召集了会议  他们会否决他
lf I called a meeting, they'd vote him down.
会是压倒性的票
It wouldn't even be close.
我不想对他做那样的事  至少不是现在
I don't want to do that to him. Not right now, anyway.
对
Yeah.
噢  我和杰克  希金斯  西蒙森说了
Oh, I did speak to Jake and Higgins, Simonsen.
他们都倾向于支持你
They're leaning towards supporting you.
- 倾向我  - 对
- Leaning? - Yeah.
- 我应该和他们聊聊吗  - 不  不  不  我会处理的
- Should I talk to them? - No, no, no. I'll handle it.
- 你确定吗  - 对
- Are you sure? - Yeah.
对
Yeah.
你知道  这对你来说是一件非常好的事
You know, this could be a very good thing for you.
对
Yeah.
抱歉
Sorry.
你去哪儿了
Where were you?
我和我爸在一起
I was with my dad.
噢  对  他怎么样
Oh, right. How is he?
挺好的
He's fine.
这一整个枪击事件很糟糕  是吧
This whole shooting thing is terrible, isn't it?
对
Yeah.
好了  这是你的晚餐  有点冷掉了
Well, this is yours. It's kinda cold now.
谢谢
Thank you.
我爸想让我做执行合伙人
My dad wants to make me managing partner.
真的吗  那太好了
Really? That's great.
对
Yeah.
那是你想要的  对不对
That's what you want, right?
当然
Sure.
那就很好啊
So it's great.
许多合伙人都怨恨我
A lot of the partners resent me.
好吧  你是个优秀的律师
Well, you're a great lawyer.
不  我有一个好的姓氏
No, I have a good last name.
不  你是个优秀的律师
No, you're a great lawyer.
你好
Hello?
嗨  苏珊娜
Hi, Suzanne.
在  等一下  你的电话
Yeah, hang on. It's for you.
- 所以你打了他吗  - 对
- So you hit him? - Right.
那熊孩子朝我吐口水  嘴里逼逼叨叨的
The kid spit on me. He was saying stuff.
你要知道  泰德  我没有在怪你  下一次
You know, Ted, I don't blame you. The next time--
他说了关于我爸爸的坏话
He was saying stum about my dad.
下一次你打架  他们就不仅仅是把你赶出来了
Next time you fight, they won't just kick you out.
他们会叫来警察把你送到青少年劳教所
They will call the police and send you to a juvenile detention center.
不是我挑起的  是他朝我吐口水
I didn't start it. The kid spit on me.
- 那不重要  - 我没有挑事
- It doesn't matter. - I didn't start it.
贝尔纳教练怎么样  我可以和他待一起吗
What about Coach Bernardo. Can I stay with him?
- 今晚不行  - 但你会问他吗
- Not tonight. - But you'll ask?
会
Yeah.
需要我开车还是
Should I drive or--
我来开
I'm driving.
- 我能跟着你吗  - 可以
- I can follow you? - Right.
或者和你一起
Or just come with you.
尼克
Nick.
早
Morning.
你昨晚什么时候回家的
What time did you get home last night?
很晚
Late.
那  一切都好吗
Well, is everything okay?
嗯  没事
Yeah, it's fine.
那个叫泰德的孩子怎么了  他怎么样了
What's up with that kid Ted? How is he?
噢  有个孩子朝他吐口水  所以他打那个孩子
Oh, some kid spit on him, so he hit him.
噢
Oh.
你现在准备去健身了吗
Are you going to the gym now?
对
Yeah.
为什么你不试着多睡一会儿呢
Why don't you just try and get some more sleep?
我睡得不多  露露
I don't sleep much, Lulu.
他要和我在一起待多久
How long would he stay with me?
几周  或者一个月
Couple of weeks, maybe a month.
一个月吗
A month?
- 直到我们为他找到寄养家庭  - 好吧
- Well, until we find him a foster family. - Right.
他应该和他熟悉的人待在一起
He should be with people that he knows.
当然  当然
Of course. Of course.
所以这是同意了吗  你愿意这么做吗
So is that a yes? You'll do it?
有件事要说明白
Here's the thing.
在这个社区里的人都相当震惊
The people in this community are pretty shaken up.
我明白
I'm sure.
我是说  你看  我知道  泰德是个很好孩子
I mean, look, I get it. Ted's a great kid.
但是我已经看到了  他们在他爸爸房子外面做了什么
But I've seen what they're doing outside his dad's house.
所以是不行吗
So that's a no?
好了  你看  我有了一个13岁的儿子  对吧
Well, you see, I've got a thirteen-year-old son, right?
他是个好孩子  安静  不怎么擅长运动
He's a good kid. He's quiet. He's not too athletic.
对
Right.
他最不需要的东西  就是在他背上画的那个靶子
The last thing he needs is to have a target painted on his back.
我是说  泰德的父亲射中了三个人  看在上帝的份上
I mean, Ted's dad shot three people, for God's sake.
这些花圈中有你送来的一个  是吗
You sent one of these arrangements, right?
对
Yeah.
嘿  你怎么样了  埃里克  还行
Hey. How you doing, Eric, okay
嗯  没事  谢谢
Yeah, fine. Thanks.
你需要什么东西吗
You need anything?
嘿  那个孩子怎么样了  休伯蒂的儿子
Hey, how's that kid, Huberty's son?
噢  他  他
Oh, he's...he's...
他没事  我猜
He's okay, I guess.
- 他的名字是泰德  对吗  - 没错
- His name is Ted, right? - That's right.
西奥多  还是  爱德华
Theodore or Edward?
西奥多
Theodore.
好
Right.
那他的父亲呢  他有没有死了
And his father, is he dead yet?
我很抱歉  埃里克
I'm very sorry, Eric.
能  能  呃  我能和你聊聊吗
Could--could--Um, could I talk to you?
当然
Sure.
能过来一下吗  失陪了
Do you mind? Excuse me.
就在这儿吧
Right here.
怎么了
What's up?
- 我有些很棒的消息  - 是吗
- I've got some great news. - Yeah?
你离开办公室之后  我越过帕拉马尔和埃尔森见面了
After you left the office, I went over to Palamar and met with Elson.
我们坐了下来  敲定了剩下的问题
We sat down, hammered out the remaining issues
并且签署了合并协议
and signed the merger agreement.
我没明白
I don't understand.
我完成了这个交易
I closed the deal.
你还不是执行总裁
You're not the CEO.
- 伯顿  - 埃里克
- Burton. - Eric....
你没有权限去签订这个合同
You don't have the authority to enter into a contract.
交易已经完成了  那还有什么问题
The deaI's done, that's what matters.
已经结束了  你处理好相关的法律问题就好了
lt's done. You'll deal with the legal technicalities.
听着  我不得不回家一趟
Look, I've gotta go home.
埃尔森想约明天见面  在你的办公室里
Elson wants to meet tomorrow, at your office,
然后谈论一些过渡条款  明白吗
and talk about a few transition issues, okay?
- 嘿  你还没和他谈吗  - 我一直在等你
- Hey. You talk to him yet? - I was waiting for you.
我们走
Let's go.
你们和贝尔纳教练谈了吗
Did you guys talk to Coach Bernardo?
泰德  你的父亲在一小时前去世了
Ted, your father died an hour ago.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
如果你愿意的话  我们可以帮你安排葬礼  或者
We can arrange a funeral if you'd like, or just...
一个葬礼吧  我想
A funeral... I guess.
你不需要现在就决定
You don't have to decide right now.
我现在想睡觉
I'm gonna go to bed now.
这与作最好的律师无关
This is not about being the best lawyer.
见鬼  我们都是好律师  这是  呃
Hell, we're all good lawyers. This is, uh...
这是有关认知  人与人之间的关系  和
This is about perceptions and relationships and...
好吧  和未来
well, the future.
对
Right.
你明白  我知道你和尼克是同期进来的
You know, I know you're a contemporary of Nick's,
但是我认为尼克有
but I do think that Nick has a--
你知道  就是有几件事  伯顿  如果你不介意
You know, just a couple things, Burton, if you don't mind.
当然不
Sure.
如果我支持这件事  我想要拿皮尔斯控股和哈尔西电子
lf I support this, I'd like to get 50% of the source credit
这两家百分之五十的客户提成
on Pierce Holdings and Halsey Electronics.
你知道这很公平 伯顿
You know it's more than fair, Burton.
可以
Fine.
好
Good.
那么
So...
现在来决定吧  让我们做一个真正艰难的抉择
Now that's decided, let's get down to real tough decisions:
是要牛肋脊还是牛腰脊
Rib eye or porterhouse?
谢谢你带我来这儿  - 不用  没事的
- Thanks for taking me here. - No, it's fine.
我开始觉得
I was starting to feel like...
我是说  我像其他人一样喜欢做爱  但是
I mean, I like sex as much as anybody likes sex, but...
我还是个女孩儿
I'm still a girl.
没错
That's right.
所以  谢谢你
So thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
我们现在可以走了
We can go now.
好
Okay.
能让我先把帐结了吗
Can I get the check, please?
- 你没事吧  - 嗯  我没事
- You all right? - Yeah, I'm fine.
你不用给我任何解释  尼古拉斯
You don't owe me any explanations, Nicholas.
不  我明白
No, I know that.
你就是这个样子
You are what you are.
你有了一个怀孕在家的女孩儿
You got a pregnant girl at home.
在缓刑期间  你现在又有了一个
On probation and now you have a...
好吧  你就这德行
Well, you are what you are.
是啊  就是这样  没错
Yeah, that's right. That's right.
你
You...
你什么都不懂
You don't have any idea.
你觉得这是我想的吗
You think this is my intention?
是吗
Do you?
你觉得这是我想要的吗  我请求她嫁给我
You think this is what I want? I asked her to marry me!
- 对 - 今晚的这个女孩  她只是
- That's right. - And this girl tonight, she's just--
那是另外一件事  那有些复杂  那只是
That's another thing that's something complicated that just--
等等  复杂吗  那是什么意思
Wait a minute. Complicated? What does that mean?
我不知道那是什么意思
I don't know what it means.
好  我知道  这不复杂  非常简单
Well, I do. It's not complicated. It's very simple.
你就是自私
You're selfish.
你什么都想要  不论什么时候  通过什么方式
You want everything you want, when you want it, how you want it.
怎么  你想我对你撒谎吗
What, you want me to lie to you?
你想我告诉你  你做了什么出色的事儿吗
You want me to tell you what a great job you're doing?
你怎么才能像个男人一样
How you're acting like a man?
我什么都不会再做了
I'm not gonna do it anymore.
你像孩子一样的行为  让我没法像对待男人一样对你
I can't treat you like a man when you act like a child.
你不能再喝酒了  尼古拉斯
You can't drink anymore, Nicholas!
你不能再吸毒了
You can't use drugs!
你也不能继续欺骗那些爱你的人了  再也不能
And you cannot continue to lie to the people who love you...anymore!
露露
Lulu?
嗯
Hmm?
你还好吗
You okay?
尼克  你怎么了
Nick, what's going on with you?
我昨晚喝酒了
I was drinking last night.
好吧
Okay.
我最近都有喝一点儿
I've been drinking a little.
发生了很多事  而且
There's been a lot going on and...
我就是喝醉了
I've just been drinking.
吸毒了吗
Drugs?
一些别的事
Something else.
好吧
Right.
关于另一个人
There's someone else.
好
Right.
苏珊娜·佩尔吗
Suzanne Pell?
对
Yeah.
为什么
Why?
- 我不知道  - 你不知道吗
- I don't know. - You don't know?
我不知道
I don't.
行
Right.
露露  我向你求婚了
Lulu, I asked you to marry me,
而你就只是看着我  好像我在羞辱你一样
and you just looked at me like I was insulting you.
你在乎苏珊娜吗
You care about Suzanne?
不  不在乎
No, not really.
你他妈的干了些什么
What the hell are you doing?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想娶你  露露  而且我想为我们孩子的做一个好爸爸
I want to marry you, Lulu, and I want to be a good father to our child.
你可以随时离开
You can just go.
任何时间  任何地点
Anytime, anywhere.
你可以带走孩子  你也可以去
You can take the child and you can just go.
告诉法庭  我是个瘾君子  是个缓刑犯  就是这样
Tell the court that I'm some addict, some probationer, and that's it.
你只要走了  我就是一个人了
You just go. And I'm alone.
我想和你组一个家
And I want to have this family.
所以你就跟苏珊娜·佩尔上床吗
So you screw Suzanne Pell?
谢了  罗伯特  慢走
Thanks, Robert. Way to go.
- 在
- Yeah?
- 嘿  埃里克  你怎么样  - 挺不错
- Hey, Eric. How are you? - Great.
坐吧
Sit down.
埃尔森在哪儿
Where's Elson?
他  呃  没有来
He's, uh, not coming.
什么
What?
埃里克  董事会成员真的都很不舒服
Eric, the board members are not real comfortable
让你管理公司
with you running the company.
- 舒服  - 对
- Comfortable? - Yeah.
几个关键的成员认为你需要  呃
Several of the key members think that you need, um...
好吧  一些时间
well, a little time.
但这是我父亲的公司  它是凯恩纸业
But it's my father's company. It's Kane Paper.
对  我理解  但这是一家由董事会经营管理的上市公司
Yeah, I understand that, but it's a publicly traded company run by a board.
现在  董事会为你父亲的离开感到遗憾
Now, that board is sorry for your loss,
但是他们并没有准备好让你担任执行总裁
but they're not prepared to make you CEO.
就算这样  我们还是要把和帕拉马尔的交易完成是吧
We're still gonna close the Palamar deal, though, right?
我不知道  我在几小时前和埃尔森的人谈过了
I don't know. I talked to Elson a couple hours ago
跟他们解释了你目前承受的压力
and explained about the stress you're under
而且你确实没有权限在合同上签字  但是  呃
and that you really didn't have the authority to sign that contract, but, uh...
好吧  我觉得他已经明白了
Well, I think he understood.
我  我不能出任执行总裁吗
I'm--I'm not gonna be CEO?
不  不  现在不能
No. No, not right now.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
好吧
Right.
说到底  你知道  也许我们可以重新回顾整件事
Down the line, you know, maybe we can revisit this whole thing...
在你有了一些更多的经验后  而且
after you've had a little more experience and...
对
Right.
我藏在桌子底下
I hid under the table.
什么
I'm sorry?
当休伯蒂进来的时候  我看到他拔出了枪
When Huberty came in, I saw him pull out the gun.
我看到他和我爸进了会议室  然后
I was in the conference room with my dad and...
我本来可以  呃
I could've, uh...
我本可以
I could've...
但我只是藏在了桌子下面
But I just hid under the table.
- 你听说了吗  - 什么
- You heard? - What?
休伯蒂死了
Huberty's dead.
- 对  - 对
- Right. - Right.
我希望他没少吃苦
I hope he suffered.
嘿
Hey.
坐吧  尼古拉斯
Sit down, Nicholas.
关于昨晚的事  我希望你能理解  那只是一个
About last night, I hope you understand that it was just a...
- 只是个什么  - 一个失误
- Just a what? - A mistake.
好  我明白
Well, I know that.
而且我明白你是在为我冒险
And I know that you've gone out on a limb for me
为了执行合伙人的事
with this managing partner thing,
我想让你知道  我不想让你失望
and I want you to know that I will not let you down.
好吧  我认为这对其他的合伙人相当不公平
Well, I don't think it's quite fair to the other partners.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
这是他们养家糊口的活儿  尼古拉斯  他们一辈子的事业
This is their livelihood, Nicholas. Their life's work.
他们必须得有一个负责任的领导人
They've gotta be sure their leader is responsible.
我会有责任感的
I will be responsible.
我现在不能这么做
I can't do it right now.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不会做的
I won't do it.
- 哦  嘿  泰德  - 嘿  教练
- Oh, hey, Ted. - Hey, Coach.
你为什么不进去  布赖恩和马西正在看电视
Why don't you come on in? Brian and Marcy are watching TV.
你怎么不和他们出去玩玩呢
Why don't you hang out with them?
谢了  贝尔纳教练
Thanks, Coach Bernardo.
- 再见  - 再见  泰德
- See you. - See you, Ted.
那么
So...
对
Yep.
你需要更多的
Do you need any more...
不用  我可以  目前来说
No, I'm okay... for now.
你需要什么可以告诉我
Just let me know what you need.
我会给你开张支票
I'll write you a check.
- 好  - 好
- Great. - Okay.
尼古拉斯尊敬地要求  我继续担任执行合伙人
Nicholas has respectfully requested that I stay on as managing partner,
在目前的这段时间
at least for the time being.
我私底下猜想过  他可能就是不想每天和老男人一起打高尔夫
I privately suspect that he just doesn't want the old man playing golf every day.
现在我很高兴的宣布我们公司的收益
Now I'm pleased to announce that our corporate revenue
在上个季度提高了百分之二十
went up 20% last last quarter.
而且杰克这儿带了两个非常重要的客户
And Jake here brought in two very important clients,
皮尔斯控股和哈尔西电子
the Pierce Holdings and Halsey Electronics.
还有  房地产部门的业绩在上个季度提高了百分之七
Also, the real estate department went up Iast quarter, 7%.
继续上升  鲍勃  很棒
Keep that up, Bob. Excellent.
对不起
I'm sorry.
真的很对不起  露露
I'm so sorry, Lulu.
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177